圣帕特里克节快乐
Happy St. Patrick's day.
送大家黑啤与爱尔兰奶油口味小蛋糕
Guinness and Irish cream cupcakes for everyone!
祝你们醉得开心
Enjoy your blackout!
这是最后12个小蛋糕了
These are the last 12 cupcakes.
其实其中两个是餐厅拿来的土豆
Actually, two of them are just potatoes from the diner.
我做累了开始偷懒
At some point I started
把糖霜加在任何能拿来充数的东西上
putting green icing on anything I could find.
麦克斯 打从上次有人
Max, we haven't been so busy since someone
在外墙上喷"免费送炮"后 就没这么忙过了
spray-painted free sex stuff on the wall outside.
瞧你还说我不懂推销
And you said I'm not good at marketing.
圣帕特里克节快乐
Happy St. Patrick's Day.
布里姬特 派崔克 小强 玛丽
Bridget, Patrick, John, Mary,
还有你 最小的 过来
And you, the little one, come over here.
我们来拿订好的小蛋糕
We're here to pick up our order.
应该订避孕药才是吧
Huh. Should be here to pick up birth control.
马上来
Coming right up.
麦克斯 我说过我很讨厌圣帕特里克节
Max, I know I told you I hated St. Patrick's Day
因为会上街庆祝的人都是醉鬼废柴
because the only people who go out are drunk trash--
请叫我们"喝茫废物"好吗
We prefer to be called "Intoxicated garbage."
但那是因为我不知道醉鬼废柴都会带现金
But that was before I knew that drunk trash carried cash.
满手绿油油的钞票 今天我最大
Nobody gonna pinch me today, 'cause I got all this green.
一捞到钱
Oh, money's involved,
你就立刻喊"爱尔兰万岁"了吗
and all of a sudden you're Erin go Bragh?
或者你应该是"小咪咪万岁"
Or in your case, "Erin go training bra"?
谁想吃小蛋糕啊
Who wants cupcakes?
今早开店做生意真是太值了
It was so worth being open this morning.
有了这笔圣帕特里克节外快
We can use this St. Patrick's Day money
我们的新枕头有着落了
to spring for some new pillows.
应该说是枕头有着落了
Or even just pillows.
也可以去酒吧里醉倒在几个肥男身上啊
Or just go to a bar and fall asleep on a couple of fat guys.
我们今天赚了多少 钱亮给姐看看
Okay, how much did we make? Show me the money.
把其余的钱也亮给姐看看
Show me the rest of the money.
好吧 我私藏了3块
Fine, I took $3.
就这么多吗
That's it?
好啦 我拿了5块
Fine, I took 5.
屌丝吃个赛百味不行啊
Can't a bitch get a foot-long?
我们都这么卖命了
But we worked so hard.
我指甲底下都弄得全绿了
I have so much green under my fingernails
看起来像我跟史莱克"爽"过了呢
It looks like I had really good sex with Shrek.
跟他除了爽 还能有别种感觉吗
What other kind could you have with him?
绿人让黑人"那里"看起来像白人的好吗
Green guys make black guys look like white guys.
我爱死圣帕特里克节了
I love St. Patrick's Day.
跟我说一个这节日的好处
Tell me one good thing about it.
早上可好[爱尔兰俚语]
Top o' the mornin'!
你看 是小憨精
Look, it's a lepre-Han.
你们觉得如何
So what do you think?
我挺担心的 你人在这里
I'm concerned. If you're out here,
那你的麦片谁看守啊
who's guarding your lucky charms?
你现在取笑我 或取笑我整晚
You laugh now, and probably all night long,
但小爷这身服装
but with this costume,
能让我泡妹上床的成功率达到最高点啊
my chances of getting laid are higher than ever.
0%的几率吗
So zero?
不 是百分之百
Nope, 100%.
你哪里来的自信
What makes you so confident?
我唯一能想到让你自信的理由是
'Cause the only answer I can think of right now
你的裤袋里有可卡因能钓毒妹
is that you have cocaine in your wee pocket.
我能理解呢
Hey, I can see it.
女人在圣帕特里克节喝到酩酊大醉
You're out drunk on St. Patrick's Day,
跟小矮妖打一炮感觉也挺不错啊
and it seems like a good idea to bang a leprechaun.
就跟总统纪念日的时候 我跟一个
Like the President's day I hooked up with a guy
穿着美国山姆大叔服的男人搞上了
dressed like Uncle Sam at the used car lot.
这套衣服是我的杀手锏
This costume is my ace in the hole.
的确是让你看起来像个傻屁精
Well, it does make you look like an ace hole.
阿憨 衣服不错啊
Nice outfit, Han.
很像我在越南时找的一个皮条客
You look like a pimp I used to use in Vietnam.
走吧 参加节日游行去
Come on, let's hit the parade.
奥列格 这里可是美国
Look, Oleg, this is America.
你可以有口音 也可以有可疑的包包
You could have an accent or a suspicious package,
但两者合一可不行[恐怖分子]
but you can't have both.
别紧张 只是我的货而已
Relax. It's just my inventory.
我要去卖T恤
I'm gonna sell T-shirts.
真让人受不了
That is revolting.
我要订五件
Put me down for five.
你可能也会对另一个产品有兴趣
You might also be interested in my other choice product.
嘘嘘斗
Pee funnels.
我也可能对这产品没兴趣
I might also not be interested in that product.
这个抛弃式的尿斗是给想像个爷们一样
It's a disposable funnel for upwardly mobile, elegant,
在街上站着撒尿的
young ladies who want to stand
上流 优雅 年轻女性使用
and pee in the street like a man.
你们也都见识过游行时的移动公厕吧
I mean, have you seen those parade port-a-potties?
何止见识过 我在里面出生的呢
Seen 'em? I was conceived in one.
把我这产品塞入裤子里
Just slip one of these babies into your pants
去公园里爱咋尿就咋尿 轻松没负担
and go pee in the park, no muss, no fuss.
其实有些小麻烦与小负担
Well, a little muss, some fuss.
并可能有十分恼人的被纸割伤问题
And possibly a very unpleasant paper cut.
真让人受不了
That's revolting.
我要订个五个
Put me down for five.
算了 六个吧 如果是女性产品
Better make it six, 'cause if it's for ladies,
阿憨肯定也需要一个
Han's definitely gonna need one.
我们跟发情期的小矮精与嘘嘘斗销售员
Max, barhopping with a horny leprechaun
去各酒吧喝酒真的好吗
and a pee funnel salesman?
太掉我的价了
Not exactly my scene.
你就不能跟迪克一起出去吗
Can't you just go with Deke?
这种事就应该跟男友去 因为他跟你一样无下限
This is boyfriend stuff, meaning he's gross like you.
是啊 可是他在个叫韦尔的地方滑雪
I know, but he's snowboarding somewhere called Vail
跟一帮所谓"家人"的人一起滑
with something called a family.
给 我们得先在肚子里垫油脂
Here, we gotta lay down a layer of grease
帮助我们吸收今晚喝下去的酒精
to absorb all the booze we'll be drinking tonight.
这能帮我们撑到半夜三点大伙碰面的时候
This'll hold us over till our 3:00 A.M. street meet,
然后我们就能挨到
which'll hold us over till our
中午过后去吃水果松饼培根蛋早饭
noon-30 rooty-tooty fresh and fruity breakfast.
来吧 开始垫胃吧
Come on, start layering.
我想念我以前过这节日的传统
I miss my old St. Patrick's Day tradition.
-想听吗 -当然不想
- Wanna hear it? - Hell, no.
在我16岁到21岁的那几年 我跟我朋友
Well, from 16 to 21, my friends and I--
也有男生哦
boys were there too,
虽然按道理是不允许他们来的
even though technically they weren't allowed--
姐16岁时 已离过三次婚
By 16, I was thrice divorced
而且还是电工协会的一员了 你继续说吧
and a member of the electricians' union, but go on.
我们在广场酒店订了大房间从上面看游行
We'd rent a big suite at The Plaza overlooking the parade,
然后我们用香槟灌满气球
and we'd fill balloons with champagne and--
砸楼下的游行群众
and throw them down at the parade crowd!
超好玩 对吧
So fun, right?
等等 原来那是你们啊
Oh, wait, that was you guys?
有一年你们砸到了我跟我朋友 阿齐
One year you hit me and my friend Archie.
他现在在罗得岛卖汽车座套
He sells car seat covers in Rhode Island now.
过得还挺不错
He's doing pretty well.
麦克斯 你为什么要在
Max, why are you dragging ass
我能骗到炮的夜晚拖拖拉拉呢
on the night I'm supposed to get some?
能别用小孩的身躯说性事吗
Stop talking about sex wearing that body.
感觉好恶心
It's gross.
我们堵在车阵里有一个小时了吧
We've been stuck in traffic for, like, an hour.
本来这时候我都喝完37瓶吉尼斯黑啤了
I could've had 37 Guinnesses by now.
并打破吉尼斯世界纪录之喝最多吉尼斯黑啤
And broken the Guinness World Record for most Guinnesses.
这台出租车有在动吗
Is this cab even moving?
这是另一家麦当劳 还是同一家
Is that a new McDonald's or the same one?
就是同一家
It's the same one,
除非门口那个打飞机的流浪汉在做巡回演出
unless that bum's on a masturbation tour of Manhattan.
开啊 让他们让路 再按喇叭
Come on! Make 'em move! Hit the horn again!
再按我的喇叭 我就砍了你的手
If you touch my horn again, I cut your hand off!
行啊 你牛逼
Okay, big shot.
砍啊 砍吧 能让我们快点到你就砍吧
Do it. Do it, if it'll get us there faster.
我知道我说过会出车钱 但这都70块了
Look, I know I said I'd spring for a cab, but it's $70!
这钱我还得拿去租快捷酒店的
And I'm gonna need that for a junior king room
小孩大床房呢
at the Holiday Inn express!
阿憨别担心 我们也会出
Don't worry, Han, we'll chip in.
我们才不出 那356块花不得
No, we won't. We need that $356.
我们今天就赚了这些
That's all we made today.
这笔钱得坚持到我们82岁呢
It has to last till we're 82.
那是我们的棺材本啊 麦克斯
This is our funeral money, Max.
不用担心 钱再赚就有嘛
Don't worry, we'll make more money.
大钱没有 小钱还是有的
Not much more, but a little bit.
我靠
Damn it!
我能听到风笛手往这方向来了
I can hear the bagpipers coming this way.
他们在吹打烊曲了
They're playing Closing Time.
表示游行结束了
That means the parade's over.
这样我永远没机会卖掉嘘嘘斗了
Now I'm never gonna sell the pee funnels.
好了 我得赶紧卖掉些T恤
All right, I gotta move some T-shirts.
走过路过不要错过
Heads up, peoples!
"亲我 我是爱尔兰人"胯下T恤 只要15块
"Kiss me I'm Irish" crotch tees. $15.
或两件25 五件60
Or two for 25! Five for 60!
你个死穷逼
You nobody!
你不能挂窗外卖东西
You can't sell those out the window.
这是违法的 得有许可证才行
That's illegal. You need a permit!
开你的车就行了 老太婆
Just drive, grandma.
俄罗斯人还自称战斗种族
I can't believe you call yourself Russian.
也不见你杀出一条血路啊
Doesn't seem like you're rushin' anywhere.
你再敢说一遍 我就把你舌头割了
You say that again, and I'll cut your tongue out!
现在又要割我舌头了吗
Oh, now you're gonna cut out my tongue?
你为何要让三角洲一带的女性失去"快乐泉源"呢
Why do you want to punish all the women in the tri-state area?
你看 天啊 是厄尔
Look, oh, my God, it's Earl!
厄尔 你在那里面干嘛
Earl, what're you doing here?
你们好啊
Hey, y'all!
这是我的风笛团体"黑爱尔兰人"
This is my bagpipe group Black Irish.
我个黑人加他们爱尔兰人
I'm black, they're Irish.
你怎么没跟我们说你会来游行
Why didn't you tell us you were coming to the parade?
我穿裙子的事我想"深藏柜中"嘛
Well, I kinda like to keep my skirt wearing on the D.L.
你什么时候学会吹风笛的啊
When did you learn how to play bagpipes?
我也不知道
I do not know.
有一次我嗑药嗑多了 等那趟旅行结束后
I took too much acid once, and, when the trip ended,
我发现我学会吹风笛跟开手动档的车了
I could play the bagpipes and drive a stick.
我们之后在布拉尼[巧言石]酒吧见吧
I'll catch up with you at Blarney's.
阿憨 付钱吧
Han, pay the man.
十个街区而已 我们能走过去
It's ten blocks away. We can walk.
-穿这鞋走吗 -穿这鞋走吗
- In these shoes? - In these shoes?
绿啤酒
Ugh, green beer.
用绿啤酒来向这个拥有过
Is this really how we honor the Irish,
许多伟大作家与诗人的国度致敬合适吗
some of our greatest writers and poets?
是他们想出来的
Oh, did they come up with,
"尿尿如果抖了抖
"If you sprinkle when you tinkle,
乖乖擦擦小便斗"吗
be a sweetie, wipe the seatie"?
首先 这不是真的诗
First of all, not a real poem.
而我作为一个跟你共用厕所的人
And as the person who shares your bathroom,
建议你身体力行那首诗
maybe take that advice.
你就甩开烦恼 大口喝酒吧
Maybe take that frown and get it drunk.
行啊 我们两个年轻貌美的姑娘
Okay, sure, we're two young girls on the town
参与美国最不安全的节日的庆典
on what's probably America's most dangerous holiday.
我们干嘛要"保持警惕"呢
Why--why have our wits about us?
就是这精神
That's the spirit.
而且说不定你能碰上爱尔兰帅哥呢
And who knows? Maybe you'll meet a cute, Irish guy.
圣帕特里克节快乐
Happy St. Paddy's Day!
布拉尼·比尔
Blarney Bill.
这间色彩缤纷的酒吧是你的吗
Are you the owner of this colorful establishment?
我身上穿着的裤子都不是我的
I'm not even the owner of these pants.
我的亲亲在哪里
Where's me kiss?
布拉尼·比尔就像是这店的吉祥物
Blarney Bill is like the mascot of this place.
每年我都让他亲求好运
Every year I kiss him for good luck.
那些好运什么时候会到位呢
And when does that luck kick in?
我的亲亲在哪里
Where's me kiss?
在我没带来的那个包包里
I left it in me other purse?
那胡子还真湿啊
Wow. That's a wet moustache.
威士忌与鱼
Scotch and fish.
什么
What?
所以才湿啊
That's why it's wet!
他最棒了
Man, he's the best.
他哪里最棒了
The best what?
姑娘们
Hey, girls!
连最后一件T恤都卖掉了
Sold my last shirt.
都说你穿小号就行
Hey, told you that small would fit.
你看阿憨在那桌跟那帮...
Look at Han at that table with all those...
我想说是"妞们"吗
I want to say "girls..."
排队想跟他合照
Waiting to take pictures with him.
贝卡
Mm, Becca!
Be-Becca!
这边
Over here.
不 你不是贝卡
Oh, no, you're not Becca.
不过... 你好吗
Hey, though.
天啊 你跟我朋友贝卡真是长得好像
Oh, my God, you look so much like my friend Becca.
你们也是在排队想跟小妖精拍照吗
Are you guys in line to take pictures with the leprechaun?
-不是 -收费5块
- No. - $5.
你说什么
Wait, what?
没错 我们是小矮妖的经纪大人与管理大人
Ah, yes, we are the leprechaun's Mcagent and Mcmanager.
跟小矮妖玩自拍收费5块
It'll be $5 to take a selfie with the leprechaun.
太划算了
That is a great deal.
-麦克斯 我不做这种生意 -好啊
- Max, I am not doing this. - Fine.
那我们唯有拿小蛋糕的钱打车回家了
Then we'll have to use the cupcake money for our cab home.
好吧 那可是只处男小矮妖
Okay, that there is virgin leprechaun.
所以起步价是10块
So it's $10.
一张照10块 亲一口15块 不许碰腰部以下
10 for a picture, 15 for a kiss, nothing below the waist.
因为腰部以下也没"东西"了
That's 'cause there's nothing below the waist.
我只有一张20块
Will you take a 20?
也行啦
I mean, I guess.
如果你是孤儿 我会对你很感性趣哟
Just so you know, if you're an orphan, I'm interested.
我什么时候成了你们的摇钱树
Are you over here making money off of me,
你们两只华尔街之狼
you wolves of Wall Street?
我们只是趁机占占酒鬼的便宜而已
We're just taking advantage of drunk people.
这可是这节日的传统
It's a St. Paddy's tradition,
就像吃咸牛肉和打警察
like corned beef or punching a cop.
那你可以让女酒鬼们也占占我的便宜吗
Well, then maybe you can get them to take advantage of me.
对"小小憨"毛手毛脚
Get a little handsy on Hansy.
我看上了那个丰满的律师助理
I've got my eye on that buxom paralegal.
那个自带鸡肉来酒吧的女人吗
The one over there who brought in outside chicken?
快帮老子牵线
Hook daddy up!
你要我去拜托那个
So I'm going up to the woman
自带两升装可乐来酒吧的抠门女
who brought her own two-liter of coke to a bar
掏钱来对你毛手毛脚吗
to ask her for money to touch you.
说到点子上了
That's the gist.
我的生活到底怎么了 我堕落到哪里了
What's happened to my life? Where am I?
布拉尼酒吧
Blarney's!
天啊 布拉尼·比尔又来了
Oh, God, it's Blarney Bill.
你在叫我吗
Hey, that's my name!
我的亲亲在哪里
Where's me kiss?
我...
Oh, well, I--
我要去厕所
I have to go to the ladies' room
把我嘴上的异味和嘴里的异物
and wash whatever is on my mouth and in my mouth
通通弄干净
off my mouth and out of my mouth.
等厕所等了这么久 害得我都想尿尿了
We've been in this line so long, now I actually have to pee.
麦克斯 你是在吃鸡肉吗
Max, are you eating chicken?
抠门女没钱逗阿憨
She didn't have 10 bucks to tickle Han,
所以她用自带的鸡肉付账
so she paid me in purse chicken.
我觉得我还赚到了呢
I think I came out ahead.
不好意思 去后面排队 不要插队
Uh, sorry, back of the line. No cuts.
拜托 我好难受
Please. I'm feeling sick.
不准插队 没有可是 不要废话
Sorry, no cuts, no buts, no coconuts.
那也是爱尔兰的名诗之一吗
Is that one of those famous Irish poems too?
我完全明白 我知道了
I totally understand. Yeah, I get it.
你就让她插队嘛 现在可是过节
Just let her cut. It's St. Patrick's Day.
不要扫人家的兴
She's having fun.
我不是故意要提我在广场酒店过节的传统
Not to bring up my St. Patrick's Day tradition at The Plaza...
又来了
Oh, good.
但那里比这地方好太多太多了
But it was so much better than this place.
比如那里上厕所不用排队
I mean, there were no lines.
我们优雅地坐在棕榈阁餐厅 浅酌鸡尾酒
We'd sit like non-animals in the Palm Court and sip bellinis.
如果你再提那个故事
I'm taking you to palm court
我就要带你去棕榈法院[阁]了
if you tell that story one more time.
两位
Guys.
我刚吐了
I just threw up.
你还小心翼翼像捧小鸡一样端过来吗
And you're carrying it around like a baby chick?
我需要漱漱口 洗把脸
I-I think I'm gonna need some water.
因为四小时后我得开校车去接小孩
I have to drive a school bus in four hours.
你真是个伟大的美国人
You're a great American.
我知道我是
I know what I am.
我的亲亲在哪里
Where's me kiss?
在她那里
Uh, she has it.
躲过一劫
Dodged a bullet.
在劫难逃
Bullet found ya.
快点 我得找别的厕所
Come on. I have to find another bathroom.
我要去一个没有布拉尼·比尔的地方尿尿
I'm not peeing anywhere near Blarney Bill.
我不想在我脱下裤子时
I don't want him to find "me kiss"
问我他的亲亲在哪里
when I have me pants down.
我把你的电话告诉他了 没关系吧
I gave him your number. Is that cool?
天啊 我觉得我撑不过去[厕所]了
Oh, no. I don't think I'm gonna make it.
你说生命吗 我也撑不下了
You mean in life? Yeah, me neither.
都怪那个绿色的啤酒
No, it's all that green beer.
如果我在53街尿裤子
And if I wet myself here on 53rd Street,,
那我就一定得丢下你 搬去中西部
I'll be forced to abandon you, move to the Midwest,
重新开始我的人生了
and start a new life.
我有个厕所你可以用
I have a bathroom you can use.
抱歉 里面还有一点鸡肉
I'm sorry, there's some chicken in it.
我今天已经掉到人生很低谷了
I've hit some very low points today,
但我绝不要在公众场所用纸鸡鸡尿尿
but I'm not about to pee through a paper penis in public.
给 麻利点 去彩车后面撒这个里面
Here, quick, just pop a squat over here behind the float,
我帮你挡着 保证没人看见
I'll block you so no one'll see,
15支高中游行乐队也会帮忙
and the 15 high school marching bands'll
掩盖掉你人生中最没下限的声音
mask the sound of you hitting rock bottom.
把那玩意给我
Gimme that thing.
我恨死你了 麦克斯
Damn it, Max. Damn it!
我该怎么做
How do I do this?
姐可是拥有公共场所随地小便的硕士学位
Well, I do have my master's in public urination from Devry.
拉开拉链 放进裤裆
Just unzip, put it in your pants,
让那一江尿水向下流吧
and let a river run through it.
没人在看我 对吧
No one's looking, right?
没人看啦
Nope.
你好啊 卡洛琳
Hi, Caroline.
苏菲 你也参加游行啦
Sophie, you were in the parade?
当然啦
Of course I was.
不去参加游行
You can't be a volunteer firefighter
怎么能带志愿消防员呢
without being in the parade.
你是一名志愿消防员吗
You're a volunteer firefighter?
我的确是自愿去的消防站
Well, I do go down to the station voluntarily.
再说了 每个消防站都需要一个波兰人[滑杆]
Besides, every fire station needs a Pole,
不就是我嘛 宝贝
and I'm it, baby.
我们都要去布拉尼酒吧
Anyway, we're all going to Blarney's.
烈酒我请客
Shots on me.
我的是指"请射我身上"[请烈酒]
And by that I mean shots on me.
走吧
Come on.
消防员的波兰杆说请你喝酒 你一定要去
When the firemen's Pole offers you drinks, you say yes.
麦克斯 打死我也不进去了
Max, I am not going back in there.
其实呢 我要请你去广场酒店喝酒
In fact, I'm treating you to a drink at The Plaza.
我之前说我们留着办葬礼的棺材本
You know that money we were saving for our funeral?
已经成为过去 因为我刚才丢脸"死"了
That's no longer an issue because I just died right then.
尿息吧 卡洛琳
Rest in pee, Caroline.
麦克斯 我们的鸡尾酒来了
Look, Max, our bellinis.
谢谢 克劳德
Thank you, Claude.
他是这酒店的名人
He's a Plaza institution.
我刚想起来他的名字是欧图
And I just remembered his name is Rolph.
你居然忘记欧图这名字
You forgot the name Rolph
我们不是才看见一个妞手里捧着"呕吐"物吗
after we just saw a girl do that in her Hands?
这里很好吧
Isn't it lovely here?
少一分嘈杂 多一分高贵
Less Blarney's, more Barney's.
相信我 这里的鸡尾酒很出名
And trust me, these bellinis are famous.
为什么 它们有拍性爱影片吗
Why? Did they make a sex tape?
味道有点像那次我把
Ooh, kind of tastes like the time
罐头黄桃放进我的盒装葡萄酒
I put canned peaches in my boxed wine.
麦克斯 这两者有云泥之别好吗
Max, a Plaza bellini is a far cry from boxed wine.
我的原则是一旦冷藏过 就是高档货
Well, my rule is, if I have to refrigerate it, it's fancy.
说你呢 电池
I'm talkin' to you, batteries.
今晚真是让我
You know, tonight is really bringing up
无比怀念过去的我
how much I miss the old me.
是啊 今晚真是让我
Yeah, tonight is really bringing up
无比怀念我的朋友阿齐
How much I miss my friend Archie.
谁
Who?
被你用香槟气球砸过的那个人
The guy you hit with the champagne balloons.
在罗得岛卖汽车座套
Sells car seat covers in Rhode Island.
你还记得我说他过得很好吗
You know how I said he was doing really well?
其实我有一年没跟他说话了
Truth is I haven't talked to him in a year.
我真是犯了个大错
Really dropped the ball.
这地方最让人兴奋的一点是
And the most exciting thing about this place--
那些电梯门随时会打开
those elevator doors can open,
你永远也不知道会是谁走出来
and you never know who's gonna step off.
麦克斯 感觉真好
Max, this is nice.
麦克斯 好无聊啊 怎么搞的
Max, this is boring. What happened?
没得搞 啥搞头都没有
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
现在我开始怀疑或许
Now I'm thinking maybe this wasn't
这里没我想得那么好玩
as much fun as I thought it was.
现在我开始怀疑阿齐死了
Now I'm thinking Archie's dead.
因为我好像收到过通知短信 但被我无视了
'cause I feel like I got a text about it and ignored it.
就连这鸡尾酒都没以前好喝了
Even this bellini doesn't taste as good.
我就知道 我的味蕾早在我吃了第一块
I knew it, my taste buds must have committed suicide
廉价寿司后就自杀了
after my first 7-11 sushi.
一切都不一样了
I mean, nothing is the same.
我以前怎么会觉得这里好玩呢
Why did I think this was fun?
因为在你遇见我之前 你根本不知道什么叫好玩
Because before you met me, you didn't know what fun was.
我懂你的意思 麦克斯
I get your point, Max,
但我以前拥有一座加勒比海小岛 和六辆水上摩托车
But I did own a Caribbean Island with six jet skis.
拜托 忘掉过去吧
Oh, come on, get over it.
干杯 现在也没那么惨
Drink up. It's not that bad.
你就不能让我自怨自艾一下吗
Can you just let me feel sad?
不行
No!
至少在圣帕特里克节不行
Not on St. Patrick's Day.
你要好好享乐
You have a good time,
不要再想不开心的事情
and you don't think about your problems.
那个吐在手里的女孩
That girl who threw up in her hands,
她也没有坐在那里抱怨 "我的人生糟透了"
she didn't sit around saying, "eh, meh, my life sucks."
她举起双手 用力一甩
No, she threw her hands in the air,
把呕吐物砸向大家
hit a lot of people with the vomit,
然后继续派对
and kept the party going.
是啊 她的"派对"都沾在大家的鞋上了
Yeah, the party was all over everybody's shoes.
听着 虽然这地方是我这辈子
Look, it doesn't matter that this is literally
去过最傻逼最做作的地方
the stupidest place I've ever been in my whole frickin' life.
但我们再点一杯40块的名导鸡尾酒
Let's get another $40 Roberto Benigni
继续我们的派对吧
and keep our party going.
算了 走吧 这里没有派对
Come on, let's go. There's no party here.
或许楼上花费三百万的犹太成人礼有派对
There may be a $3 million bat mitzvah happening upstairs,
但咱们这里绝对没有
but there's no party here.
但我知道哪里会有
But I do know where there is one.
麻烦结账 欧图
We'll just take the check, Rolph.
我突然又想起来他应该叫丹尼斯
And I just remembered his name is Dennis.
麦克斯 抱歉在你过节的时候倒苦水
Max, I'm sorry if I rained on your parade today.
好吧 是尿
Well, peed on it.
别担心
Don't worry about it.
一切对我来说有意义的东西 都会被尿
Everything that means something to me gets peed on.
姑娘们 听说你们走了
Hey, girls! I heard you left!
你们错过我赢得呼啦圈大赛那一刻
You missed me winning the hula-hooping contest.
你什么时候学会扭呼啦圈了
When did you learn how to hula-hoop?
再说一遍 我不知道
Once again, I do not know.
你这身风笛手服还是很好看啊
You're still rocking the bagpipe ensemble.
你不是说你穿裙子的事
I thought you wanted to keep
想要保持低调 "深锁柜中"吗
your skirt wearing on the low-low.
在我感受到我裙底的风"笛"与风"囊"
That was before I discovered the sensation
被凉风吹过的爽快感后 我就无所谓了
of a cool breeze circling my bag and my pipe.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Hey! Max, Caroline!
不好意思 借过 借过
Excuse me, move it. Move it. Move it.
让开 想弄坏老娘超大的三叶草吗
Hey, move it. Wanna break my big-ass clover?
姑娘们 你们去哪里了
Girls, where did you go?
我们去了广场酒店 然后我发现
We went to The Plaza, and I realized my life
心灵的富有比金钱更让我感到富有
may actually be richer now than when I was rich.
不是吧 已经来不及抽身了吗
Oh, no. Is it too late to walk away?
你们俩能借我点现金吗
Can you girls loan me some cash?
我泡到了一个女孩 我从她姐姐在
I met a girl, and I need money for the bus
新泽西的公寓回来时 需要一点公车费
back from her sister's condo in Jersey city.
她说不能太大声 我说这我可不能保证
She said we've got to be quiet, but I make no promises.
我支持你 阿憨 你需要多少 20块吗
Sure. I gotcha, Han. What do you need, a 20?
管它的 拿50块去吧 钱还可以再赚
Oh, what the hell? Take 50. We can always make more.
或赚不到了
Or not.
瞧你撒钱的样子
Look at you throwing the cash around.
美女 人生路上说不定还有希望呢
You know, girl, there might be hope for you yet.
珍宁 我准备好啦
Jeanine, I'm good to go.
我就跟你们说了 百分之百
Told you, girls. 100%.
看来今晚他们俩都要"不爽"一发了
Looks like they're both gonna get unlucky tonight.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 这边
Hey, Max, Caroline, over here!
我帮你们留了位置
I save ya a couple of seats.
还留了几个消防员
And a couple of firemen.
没有位置坐啊
Uh, there's no place to sit.
你真是太嫩了
Oh, you are so green.
你好
'Sup?
圣帕特里克节快乐 我的亲亲在哪里
Happy st. Paddy's day! Where's me kiss?
威士忌与鱼啊
Scotch and fish!